allindiansite.com 2010-11-19

# Telugu songs, Telugu Music, Telugu Radio, Telugu Movies from AllIndianSite.com - It's All About Telugu Songs, Telugu Music

|  **Privacy Statement for AllIndianSite.com**  
AllIndianSite.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: AllIndianSite.com 

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

**Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. Cookies are not used for any purpose other than ad management.

**Advertisers**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp   
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.  
We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml 

**Personal Information**  
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. AllIndianSite.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. All our data is password protected and is never let out or sold to any third pary whatsoever. 

---|---|---
